tmxmoney.com 2012-10-21

# Privacy Policy | TMX Group

This privacy policy sets out the information gathering and dissemination practices of TMX Group Inc. ("TMX Group") and its affiliates and subsidiaries, including, where applicable, TSX Inc., TSX Venture Exchange Inc., Montreal Exchange Inc., Canadian Derivatives Clearing Corporation, The Equicom Group Inc., Natural Gas Exchange Inc. and Shorcan Brokers Limited (collectively, the "TMX" or "we") in the use of the TMX.com and/or TMXmoney.com websites, located at www.tmx.com and www.tmxmoney.com respectively (collectively, "the Websites"). By using the Websites, you are consenting to this privacy policy and the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by TMX as outlined in this privacy policy. If this privacy policy is not acceptable to you, please do not submit any of your personal information.

We may update this privacy policy from time to time and you are responsible for periodically reviewing the most current version of this privacy policy on the Websites. Your continued use of the Websites or submission of information will be deemed your conclusive acceptance of the updated privacy policy.

In this Privacy Policy, the phrase "Service Providers" includes, but is not limited to, any licensors, suppliers, information providers or other third parties that provide, from time to time, any data, information, content, application, tool or service for purposes of the Websites.

#### Collecting, Using and Disclosing Information

This privacy policy describes our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of the personal information that we (or our Service Providers on our behalf) collect about you on the Websites such as your name, address, phone number, fax number, e-mail address or payment information. We may collect this information when you subscribe to, or sign your company up for, certain services, tools or features that we provide, when you register for seminars or other programs that we offer, when you fill out forms made available through the Websites, when you enter a promotion or contest, when you complete a survey, when you e-mail us with general inquiries or with your comments or suggestions, or otherwise in connection with your use of the Websites. We will limit the personal information we collect to what we need for the purposes for which it was collected, and will use such personal information for such purposes. We may also use personal information we collect to provide you with information on products, services and events that we or third parties offer that we believe may be of interest to you. If we wish to use your personal information for any other purpose, we will obtain your consent before using the information.

#### Storing of Information and Restricting Access

We may store your personal information (in encrypted form where we believe it to be highly sensitive) in electronic databases or e-mail boxes hosted by us or our Service Providers, for periods of time and with safeguards that we believe are reasonable depending on the nature and sensitivity of the information. Access to the information is restricted in accordance with our security protocols.

Certain features on the Websites are password-protected to prevent unauthorized access. You are responsible for the confidentiality and use of such passwords.

Due to the nature of Internet communications and evolving technologies, TMX cannot provide assurance that the personal information we collect will remain free from loss, interception, misuse or alteration by third parties and TMX and its Service Providers shall have no liability for any loss, interception, misuse or alteration.

#### Automatic Collection of Information

In some cases, we may collect information about you that may or may not be personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include your Internet protocol (IP) address, the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the advertisement or domain name of the website from which you linked to the Websites. The collection, use, disclosure and storage of such information will be in accordance with this privacy policy, including for the purpose of optimizing Website user experience.

#### Cookies

Some pages on the Websites use a technology called "cookies". A cookie is a token that a server gives to your browser when you access a website. Cookies are capable of storing many types of data. Cookies may be placed by TMX or a third party. Cookies help provide additional functionality to the Websites or help provide and analyze Website traffic and usage information. For instance, our server may set a cookie that keeps you from having to enter a password more than once during a visit to one of the Websites. In all cases in which cookies are used, we will not collect personally-identifiable information except with your permission. With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

#### Releasing Information

We may provide your personal information to other persons but only if:

  * we have your consent;
  * we provide the information to Service Providers who assist us in serving you and who have agreed to appropriate contractual provisions regarding the protection of personal information in accordance with applicable law; or
  * we are required to do so by law, regulation or court order.

We may send your personal information outside of the country for the purposes set out herein, including for process and storage by Service Providers in connection with such purposes, and you should note that while such information is out of the country, it is subject to the laws of the country in which it is held, and may be subject to disclosure to the governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory agencies of such other country, pursuant to the laws of such country.

#### Respecting and Responding to Your Privacy Concerns

You have the option to refuse or withdraw consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, and we will respect your choices. If you wish to exercise this option or if you have any questions or enquiries with respect to our privacy policies or procedures, please send a written request to: Chief Privacy Officer, TMX Group, The Exchange Tower, 130 King Street West, Toronto, Canada, M5X 1J2. We will investigate and respond to your concerns about any aspect of our handling of your information.

If you wish to edit and/or delete your information related to the Portfolio or Alerts feature on our Websites (including changing your settings such that you no longer receive Alerts), you may do so online through the Portfolio and Alerts section on TMXmoney.com. 

BY USING THE WEBSITES, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY, UNDERSTAND IT AND AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
